(upbeat music)
♪ Livin' easy ♪
♪ Lovin' free ♪
♪ Season ticket on a one way ride ♪
♪ Askin' nothin' ♪
♪ Leave me be ♪
♪ Takin' everythin' in my stride ♪
♪ Don't need reason ♪
♪ Don't need rhyme ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' that I'd rather do ♪
♪ Goin' down ♪
♪ Party time ♪
♪ My friends are gonna be there too ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell ♪
♪ On the highway to hell ♪
♪ Highway to hell ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell ♪
♪ No stop signs ♪
♪ Speed limit ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna slow me down ♪
♪ Like a wheel ♪
♪ Gonna spin it ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna mess me around ♪
♪ Hey Satan ♪
♪ Payin' my dues ♪
♪ Playin' in a rockin' band ♪
♪ Hey mamma ♪
♪ Look at me ♪
♪ I'm on the way to the promised land ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell ♪
♪ Highway to hell ♪
♪ Don't stop me ♪
♪ Ah ah ah ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell ♪
♪ On the highway to hell ♪
♪ Highway to hell ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Highway to hell ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell ♪
♪ Ah highway to hell ♪
♪ Highway to hell ♪
♪ And I'm goin' down ♪
♪ All the way ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell ♪